EDDIE YEUNG

(510) 813-0317 <u>eycs0317@gmail.com</u> 18010 Incline Road, Hayward,CA 94541

PROFILE

Automotive Service Advisor with 16 years of experience in Automotive Industry. I have great experience in high volume dealership and maintain top 5% in CSI among all Lexus Dealer. Friendly and resourceful with strong listening skills and the ability to ask the right questions to assist technicians with diagnosis. Effectively builds loyal and long-term relationships with customers.

EXPERIENCE

Service Advisor - Lexus of Serramonte - Daly City, CA — 2009 - 2020

Internal Service Advisor - Lexus of Serramonte - Daly City, CA — 2007 - 2009

Loaner Car Manager/Porter Manager - Lexus of Serramonte - Daly City, CA 2005 - 2007

Porter - Lexus of Serramonte - Daly City, CA — 2004-2005

EDUCATION

De Anza College - Automobile/Automotive Mechanics Technology/ Technician

SKILLS

- Strong Customer Service
- Customer Relations
- Creative Problem Solving
- Time Management
- ADP, Word, Excel, Dealer Logic